clipquiz.net 2018-07-05

# 

Our site is taken very seriously by the confidentiality of your data, and we do not in any way save your information. The text is presented in order to disclose the privacy policy for the application that is used at www.clipquiz.net.

Details our privacy policy as www.clipquiz.net collects, stores and uses the information collected through the application. www.clipquiz.net guarantees the confidentiality of the personal information that you provide to us when entering our website, you can be sure that we will never store and disclose your personal information to third parties.

www.clipquiz.net agrees not to misuse the information provided by the user through the application, as authorizations through the Facebook dialog are ordered, you can be sure that the information will only be used in accordance with this policy.

www.clipquiz.net may change its policies at any time through this section. This privacy policy was updated on March 4, 2018. If we make changes to the website, it may also be policy changes and it is your duty to review these changes to ensure that it complies with all of the terms of our policies.

information used  
We collect basic information about your profile, especially the name, profile photos and Facebook ID to get the profile picture used in certain tests.

We need this information to understand your needs and improve the user experience with the application, and in particular to create fun photo to later be shared with your friends on Facebook.

confidentiality  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your information to third parties.

We guarantee and assure the best way possible that your information is safe. The use of the information is temporary pending the results of the tests are processed, and are never stored by us.

Will they disclose the information to third parties?  
We will not sell, market or otherwise transfer your information to third parties.  
www.clipquiz.net is not responsible for any illegal activity on Facebook. We do not have any information about Facebook. By using this website, you are complying with our policies.

web cookies  
This website can also host web cookies. Web cookies are typically small pixel-by-pixel, visible or invisible images placed within the source code of a site's pages. cookies are used and used in a similar way to cookies. In addition, Web cookies are typically used to measure the traffic of users who visit a site and can design a pattern of users of a website.

Third Party Advertising and Cookies:  
Advertising companies may use and collect anonymous information about their interests to customize the content of the advertisements. Information such as location or interests can be connected to your device but is not connected to your identity. These companies have their own privacy policies. Click the links to view the policies of these sites:

The results of this page are merely as a form of entertainment and fun, and should not be taken as serious results. Calculations are based on the interactions of people in your timeline, such as likes, comments, and posts.
